{'tokens': ['Police', 'officials', 'said', 'officers', 'will', 'wear', 'body', 'cameras', '-', 'and', 'many', 'will', 'wear', 'shorts', 'and', 'ride', 'bikes', 'or', 'horses', 'in', 'a', 'deliberate', 'effort', 'not', 'to', 'appear', 'confrontational', '.', 'If', 'officers', 'don', 'riot', 'gear', ',', 'which', 'is', 'incompatible', 'with', 'the', 'cameras', ',', 'special', 'police', 'video', 'crews', 'are', 'to', 'accompany', 'them', '.'], 'pos': ['NN', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'NNS', 'MD', 'VB', 'NN', 'NNS', ':', 'CC', 'JJ', 'MD', 'VB', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'RB', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', '.', 'IN', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'WDT', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', ',', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-07_cleveland-shakes-off-rust-before_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['With', 'the', 'Middle', 'East', 'in', 'tumult', ',', 'radical', 'groups', 'holding', 'large', 'parts', 'of', 'Africa', ',', 'and', 'a', 'presidential', 'campaign', 'fanning', 'fears', 'of', 'a', 'growing', 'terrorism', 'threat', ',', 'the', 'White', 'House', 'has', 'steadily', 'expanded', 'the', 'global', 'missions', 'of', 'American', 'Special', 'Operations', 'troops', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'VBG', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2015-12-29_u-s-commandos-take-on-larger-rol_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['A', ':', 'Well', ',', 'I', 'think', 'he', 'has', 'a', 'lot', 'of', 'people', 'afraid', ',', 'and', 'I', 'think', 'not', 'just', 'people', 'who', 'are', 'undocumented', ',', 'but', 'people', 'who', 'are', 'just', 'citizens', 'of', 'this', 'country', ',', 'American', 'citizens', '.', 'He', 'has', 'them', 'completely', 'scared', '.', '...', 'I', 'do', "n't", 'know', 'how', 'you', "'re", 'going', 'to', 'round', 'up', '11', 'million', 'people', 'and', 'deport', 'them', 'all', '.', 'And', 'I', 'do', "n't", 'see', 'how', 'that', 'can', 'be', 'good', 'for', 'our', 'economy', 'and', 'certainly', 'not', 'for', 'families', 'and', 'I', 'just', 'do', "n't", 'think', 'it', "'s", 'a', 'good', 'thing', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', ':', 'UH', ',', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'JJ', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'RB', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBP', 'JJ', ',', 'CC', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', '.', ':', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'TO', 'VB', 'RP', 'CD', 'CD', 'NNS', 'CC', 'VB', 'PRP', 'DT', '.', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'WRB', 'WDT', 'MD', 'VB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'CC', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-05-06_immigration-debate-hits-home-for_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Why', 'had', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'called', 'into', 'Bill', "O'Reilly", "'s", 'program', 'on', 'Fox', 'News', ',', 'resulting', 'in', 'the', 'network', 'cutting', 'away', 'from', 'the', 'emotionally', 'resonant', 'remarks', 'by', 'Patricia', 'Smith', ',', 'whose', 'son', 'Sean', 'was', 'killed', 'in', 'the', '2012', 'attacks', 'in', 'Benghazi', ',', 'Libya', '?'], 'pos': ['WRB', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBG', 'RP', 'IN', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'WP$', 'NN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-07-20_beyond-plagiarism-a-bigger-issue_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['10:30', 'a.m.', 'Donald', 'Trump', 'has', 'traded', 'his', 'usual', 'large-scale', 'rallies', 'for', 'an', 'intimate', 'town', 'hall', 'setting', '.'], 'pos': ['CD', 'RB', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['TIME', 'TIME', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-02-08_the-latest-nh-towns-cast-first-v_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'Democratic', 'race', 'has', 'taken', 'a', 'turn', 'for', 'the', 'nasty', 'as', 'Clinton', 'and', 'Sanders', 'explore', 'their', 'newfound', 'aggressiveness', ',', 'each', 'suddenly', 'willing', 'to', 'get', 'personal', 'as', 'Sanders', 'rides', 'an', 'impressive', 'winning', 'streak', 'and', 'as', 'Clinton', 'readies', 'for', 'her', 'own', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'IN', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'CC', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-04-11_clinton-and-sanders-trade-low-bl_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Tuesday', "'s", 'contests', '--', 'Clinton', 'won', 'in', 'Delaware', ',', 'Connecticut', ',', 'Maryland', 'and', 'Pennsylvania', ',', 'while', 'Sanders', 'won', 'Rhode', 'Island', '--', 'gave', 'Clinton', 'a', 'nearly', 'insurmountable', 'lead', 'in', 'pledged', 'delegates', ',', 'and', 'she', 'already', 'was', 'way', 'ahead', 'of', 'Sanders', 'in', 'superdelegates', ',', 'the', 'unpledged', 'party', 'leaders', 'and', 'officials', 'who', 'may', 'support', 'the', 'candidate', 'of', 'their', 'choice', 'at', 'the', 'convention', '.', 'As', 'of', 'Wednesday', ',', 'Clinton', 'had', '90', '%', 'of', 'the', 'delegates', 'needed', 'to', 'clinch', 'the', 'nomination', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'POS', 'NNS', ':', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', ',', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', ':', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBN', 'NNS', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'NN', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNS', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', 'WP', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.', 'IN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'CD', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERCENT', 'PERCENT', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-04-28_sanders-lays-off-more-than-campa_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['Standing', 'alongside', 'labor', 'leader', 'and', 'civil', 'rights', 'activist', 'Dolores', 'Huerta', ',', 'who', 'co-founded', 'the', 'United', 'Farm', 'Workers', ',', 'and', 'Dream', 'Act', 'activist', 'Dan-el', 'Padilla', 'Peralta', ',', 'Mark-Viverito', 'accused', 'Sanders', 'of', 'being', 'inactive', 'in', 'the', 'years-long', 'effort', 'for', 'comprehensive', 'immigration', 'reform', 'and', 'chided', 'him', 'for', 'siding', 'with', 'Republicans', '.'], 'pos': ['VBG', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNPS', ',', 'CC', 'NN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'IN', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'CC', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNPS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-04-13_standing-with-activists-mark-viv_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['At', 'Clinton', "'s", 'New', 'York', 'campaign', 'headquarters', ',', 'her', 'advisers', 'are', 'grappling', 'with', 'how', 'to', 'convince', 'swing', 'voters', 'that', 'a', 'former', 'secretary', 'of', 'state', ',', 'senator', 'and', 'first', 'lady', 'who', 'owns', 'a', 'home', 'in', 'Washington', ',', 'has', 'cultivated', 'deep', 'ties', 'to', 'Wall', 'Street', 'and', 'has', 'played', 'a', 'starring', 'role', 'in', 'the', 'political', 'scene', 'for', 'a', 'quarter-century', 'would', 'usher', 'in', 'change', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'IN', 'WRB', 'TO', 'VB', 'NN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'NN', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'CC', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'DT', 'VBG', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'MD', 'VB', 'IN', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-01_voters-skeptical-as-clinton-vows_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['Indeed', ',', 'proponents', 'of', 'more', 'controls', 'on', 'hate', 'speech', 'here', 'say', 'there', 'is', 'a', 'direct', 'correlation', 'to', 'the', 'vitriol', 'now', 'flying', 'in', 'the', 'German', 'public', 'domain', 'and', 'the', 'sharp', 'spike', 'of', 'attacks', 'on', 'refugee', 'centers', '.', 'Last', 'year', ',', 'German', 'police', 'reported', '906', 'attacks', 'against', 'asylum', 'seeker', 'homes', ',', 'ranging', 'from', 'arson', 'to', 'physical', 'assaults', '.', 'The', 'figure', 'amounts', 'to', 'more', 'than', 'a', 'fourfold', 'increase', ',', 'compared', 'with', '2014', 'numbers', '.'], 'pos': ['RB', ',', 'NNS', 'IN', 'JJR', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', 'RB', 'VBP', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'RB', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', '.', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBD', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNS', ',', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'JJR', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'VBN', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-01-07_germany-targets-a-surge-of-vitri_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Demonstrators', 'picket', 'every', 'political', 'convention', ',', 'but', 'there', 'is', 'added', 'security', 'concern', 'here', 'because', 'punches', 'have', 'already', 'been', 'thrown', 'at', 'Trump', 'rallies', '-', 'including', 'last', 'week', 'in', 'San', 'Jose', '.', 'Cleveland', 'police', 'have', 'insisted', 'they', 'are', 'prepared', 'for', 'the', 'thousands', 'of', 'people', 'who', 'love', 'Trump', 'sharing', 'the', 'streets', 'with', 'thousands', 'who', 'detest', 'him', '.'], 'pos': ['NNS', 'NN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'NN', 'NN', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNS', ':', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBP', 'NNP', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBP', 'PRP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-07_cleveland-shakes-off-rust-before_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['Cruz', ',', 'a', 'graduate', 'of', 'Harvard', 'Law', 'School', 'who', 'has', 'succesfully', 'argued', 'a', 'number', 'of', 'cases', 'before', 'the', 'United', 'States', 'Supreme', 'Court', ',', 'will', 'do', 'an', 'excellent', 'job', 'in', 'judicial', 'appointments', ',', 'Blackwell', 'maintains', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNPS', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', 'NNP', 'VBZ', '.'], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-01-10_conservative-icon-morton-blackwe_d473'}
{'tokens': ['She', 'went', 'on', 'to', 'attack', 'Donald', 'Trump', ',', 'saying', 'the', 'presumptive', 'Republican', 'nominee', '``', 'has', "n't", 'given', 'this', 'issue', 'much', 'thought', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['PRP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'VBG', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', '``', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'politico_2016-05-11_clinton-i-support-d-c-statehood_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['In', 'political', 'theory', ',', 'it', "'s", 'known', 'as', '``', 'issue', 'ownership', "''", ':', 'to', 'be', 'known', 'to', 'voters', 'as', 'the', 'party', 'that', 'cares', 'most', 'about', 'something', ',', 'and', 'is', 'best', 'at', 'it', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'IN', '``', 'NN', 'NN', "''", ':', 'TO', 'VB', 'VBN', 'TO', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBZ', 'RBS', 'RB', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'IN', 'PRP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2015-12-01_for-gop-a-golden-opportunity-to-_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'number', 'of', 'people', 'The', 'Washington', 'Post', 'reported', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', 'is', 'actively', 'vetting', 'to', 'be', 'her', 'running', 'mate', '.', '7.7', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBG', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', '.', 'CD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-27_byline-amber-phillips_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['Others', 'are', 'even', 'more', 'skeptical', '.', "''", 'I', 'can', 'see', 'the', 'argument', 'for', 'it', ',', 'but', 'I', "'m", 'not', 'betting', 'on', 'a', 'deal', ',', "''", 'Mr.', 'Mahaney', 'said', '.', "''", 'There', 'just', 'are', "n't", 'many', 'logical', 'buyers', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['NNS', 'VBP', 'RB', 'RBR', 'JJ', '.', "''", 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', '.', "''", 'EX', 'RB', 'VBP', 'RB', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-06-17_as-its-rivals-pair-up-will-twitt_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['This', 'is', 'the', 'first', 'win', 'for', 'Cruz', 'during', 'the', 'group', 'of', 'Super', 'Tuesday', 'contests', 'and', 'his', 'second', 'win', 'since', 'the', 'leadoff', 'Iowa', 'caucuses', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'VBP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-03-01_the-latest-sanders-wins-minnesot_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['Rob', 'Billeaud', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-08-31_abedin-needs-to-get-out-of-two-r_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Other', 'experts', 'cautioned', 'that', 'even', 'if', 'Mr.', 'Trump', 'does', 'retain', 'substantial', 'support', 'among', 'white', 'male', 'union', 'members', 'without', 'college', 'degrees', ',', 'that', 'will', 'not', 'necessarily', 'yield', 'him', 'an', 'electoral', 'advantage', 'in', 'November', 'if', 'he', 'becomes', 'the', 'Republican', 'nominee', '.'], 'pos': ['JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'IN', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VB', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', ',', 'WDT', 'MD', 'RB', 'RB', 'VB', 'PRP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-01-30_traditionally-democrat-unions-ar_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'Time', 'is', 'always', 'a', 'challenge', 'for', 'us', ',', 'but', 'we', "'re", 'in', 'good', 'position', 'to', 'make', 'a', 'run', ',', "''", 'he', 'said', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', ',', "''", 'PRP', 'VBD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-02-17_sanders-and-clinton-see-black-vo_d473'}
{'tokens': ['What', 'was', 'once', 'subtext', 'is', 'now', 'a', 'full', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'political', 'conversation', '.'], 'pos': ['WP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-04-28_with-woman-s-card-trump-escalate_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'I', 'am', 'personally', 'open', '-', 'after', 'all', 'that', 'has', 'happened', 'and', 'after', '10', 'years', 'in', 'that', 'probationary', 'status', 'where', 'all', 'they', 'have', 'is', 'a', 'permit', '-', 'I', 'personally', 'am', 'open', 'to', 'allowing', 'people', 'to', 'apply', 'for', 'a', 'green', 'card', ',', "''", 'Rubio', 'said', ',', 'talking', 'about', 'his', 'views', 'on', 'whether', 'and', 'how', 'to', 'offer', 'legal', 'status', 'to', 'immigrants', 'who', 'entered', 'the', 'country', 'illegally', '.', 'Then', 'the', 'caveat', ':', 'He', 'is', 'also', 'open', 'to', 'notfollowing', 'his', 'own', 'personal', 'views', '.', 'If', 'that', "'s", 'what', 'people', 'want', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'JJ', ':', 'IN', 'DT', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'CC', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WRB', 'DT', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', ':', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBP', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VBG', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'VBD', ',', 'VBG', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'IN', 'CC', 'WRB', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'RB', '.', 'RB', 'DT', 'NN', ':', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'IN', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'WP', 'NNS', 'VBP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2015-12-20_marco-rubio-s-strategic-stances_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['Trump', 'thanked', 'his', 'parents', ',', 'his', 'siblings', ',', 'his', 'wife', 'and', 'his', 'children', ',', 'as', 'well', 'as', 'his', 'campaign', 'manager', ',', 'Corey', 'Lewandowski', ',', 'and', 'his', 'spokeswoman', ',', 'Hope', 'Hicks', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'VBD', 'PRP$', 'NNS', ',', 'PRP$', 'NNS', ',', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'NNS', ',', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-02-09_trump-we-are-going-to-win-so-muc_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['Not', 'far', 'away', ',', 'brothers', 'John', 'and', 'Brian', 'Meza', ',', '22', 'and', '19', ',', 'were', 'talking', 'about', 'why', 'they', 'had', 'come', 'to', 'Sanders', 'and', 'why', 'their', 'elders', 'had', 'not', '.'], 'pos': ['RB', 'RB', 'RB', ',', 'NNS', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'CD', 'CC', 'CD', ',', 'VBD', 'VBG', 'IN', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'CC', 'WRB', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'RB', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-05_is-sanders-finally-connecting-wi_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['Sanders', ',', 'accordingly', ',', 'is', 'counting', 'on', 'something', 'dramatic', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', ',', 'RB', ',', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NN', 'JJ', '.'], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-03-23_sanders-scrambles-to-keep-pace-w_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'He', 'does', 'need', 'to', 'come', 'up', 'with', 'that', 'statement', ',', "''", 'said', 'Bruce', 'Hough', ',', 'the', 'Republican', 'National', 'Committeeman', 'from', 'Utah', '.', '``', 'I', 'think', 'Paul', 'Ryan', 'is', 'using', 'his', 'position', 'of', 'leadership', 'to', 'say', ',', 'this', 'is', 'a', 'great', 'time', 'to', 'really', 'show', 'everyone', 'that', 'you', 'can', 'unify', 'the', 'party', 'by', 'delivering', 'the', 'right', 'messages', 'and', 'delivering', 'them', 'the', 'right', 'way', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'VB', 'TO', 'VB', 'RP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', "''", 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', ',', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'RB', 'VB', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'VBG', 'PRP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-cue', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'politico_2016-05-05_paul-ryan-says-he-s-not-ready-to_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['In', 'a', 'back-and-forth', 'email', 'thread', 'with', 'Cruz', "'s", 'campaign', ',', 'Breitbart', 'News', 'asked', 'several', 'times', 'whether', 'Sen.', 'Cruz', 'disavowed', 'Lindsey', 'Graham', "'s", 'endorsement', ',', 'but', 'the', 'campaign', 'refused', 'to', 'answer', 'on', 'multiple', 'occasions', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBD', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-03-20_ted-cruz-refuses-to-disavow-lind_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Trump', "'s", 'handling', 'of', 'the', 'unfolding', 'events', 'on', 'Sunday', '-', 'private', 'consultation', 'with', 'aides', 'while', 'issuing', 'a', 'flurry', 'of', 'proclamations', 'and', 'comments', 'on', 'social', 'media', '-', 'is', 'reflective', 'of', 'how', 'he', 'often', 'handles', 'breaking', 'news', '.', 'While', 'he', 'works', 'closely', 'with', 'advisers', 'to', 'craft', 'the', 'theme', 'of', 'public', 'remarks', 'and', 'statements', ',', 'he', 'believes', 'it', 'is', 'also', 'crucial', 'for', 'him', 'to', 'be', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'national', 'conversation', 'as', 'soon', 'as', 'possible', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'VBG', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', ':', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', ':', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'IN', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'NN', '.', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', ',', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'PRP', 'TO', 'VB', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'JJ', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-13_responses-are-in-keeping-with-ca_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['In', 'each', 'of', 'those', 'states', ',', 'about', 'a', 'third', 'of', 'Democratic', 'voters', 'or', 'less', 'want', 'a', 'switch', 'to', 'more', 'liberal', 'policies', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'JJR', 'VBP', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'JJR', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-03-01_the-latest-sanders-wins-minnesot_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['South', 'Carolina', ':', 'Andrew', 'Collins', ',', 'Antjuan', 'Seawright', ',', 'Barry', 'Wynn', ',', 'Bob', 'McAlister', ',', 'Boyd', 'Brown', ',', 'Brady', 'Quirk-Garvan', ',', 'Bruce', 'Haynes', ',', 'Catherine', 'Templeton', ',', 'Chad', 'Connelly', ',', 'Chip', 'Felkel', ',', 'Cindy', 'Costa', ',', 'Clay', 'Middleton', ',', 'David', 'Wilkins', ',', 'Dick', 'Harpootlian', ',', 'Donna', 'Hicks', ',', 'Drea', 'Byars', ',', 'Ed', 'McMullen', ',', 'Elizabeth', 'Colbert-Busch', ',', 'Ellen', 'Weaver', ',', 'Erin', 'McKee', ',', 'Gary', 'R.', 'Smith', ',', 'Glenn', 'McCall', ',', 'Inez', 'Tenenbaum', ',', 'Isaiah', 'Nelson', ',', 'Jaime', 'R.', 'Harrison', ',', 'James', 'Smith', ',', 'Jason', 'Perkey', ',', 'Jay', 'W.', 'Ragley', ',', 'Jim', 'Hodges', ',', 'Jimmy', 'Williams', ',', 'Joe', 'Erwin', ',', 'Joel', 'Sawyer', ',', 'John', 'Brisini', ',', 'Kevin', 'Bishop', ',', 'Kim', 'Wellman', ',', 'Laurin', 'Manning', ',', 'Le', 'Frye', ',', 'Luke', 'Byars', ',', 'Matt', 'Moore', ',', 'Mikee', 'Johnson', ',', 'Morgan', 'Allison', ',', 'Phil', 'Noble', ',', 'Scott', 'Farmer', ',', 'Tony', 'Denny', ',', 'Trey', 'Walker', ',', 'Tyler', 'Jones', ',', 'Walter', 'Whetsell', ',', 'Warren', 'Tompkins', ',', 'Will', 'Folks', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', ':', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-02-04_insiders-trump-will-rebound-in-n_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'The', 'sixth', 'bloc', 'is', 'the', 'establishment', 'and', 'moderate', 'Republicans.The', 'only', 'one', 'that', 'can', 'unite', 'the', 'party', 'in', 'all', '6', 'principle', 'voting', 'blocs', 'is', 'Cruz', ',', "''", 'Viguerie', 'adds', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NN', 'RB', 'CD', 'WDT', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'CD', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'VBZ', 'NNP', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'VBZ', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-01-19_long-time-leaders-of-conservativ_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['Zimmerman', ',', '32', ',', 'noted', 'the', 'Justice', 'Department', 'returned', 'the', 'weapon', 'to', 'him', 'recently', 'and', 'it', 'still', 'bears', 'the', 'case', 'number', 'written', 'on', 'it', 'in', 'silver', 'permanent', 'marker', '.', '``', 'This', 'is', 'a', 'piece', 'of', 'American', 'History', ',', "''", 'he', 'wrote', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', ',', 'CD', ',', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'PRP', 'RB', 'CC', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'IN', 'NN', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', '``', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'PRP', 'VBD', '.'], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-05-13_auction-of-gun-used-to-kill-tray_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Radio', 'talk', 'show', 'host', 'Glenn', 'Beck', 'minced', 'no', 'words', 'Tuesday', 'night', 'in', 'sharing', 'what', 'he', 'thinks', 'of', 'Sarah', 'Palin', "'s", 'endorsement', 'of', 'Donald', 'Trump', '.'], 'pos': ['NN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNS', 'NNP', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'WP', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'TIME', 'TIME', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'west-journal_2016-01-20_wow-glenn-beck-just-responded-to_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'policy-making', 'elite', ',', 'on', 'the', 'other', 'hand', ',', 'know', 'that', "''", 'strategic', 'thinking', 'includes', 'the', 'notion', 'that', 'you', 'have', 'to', 'build', 'a', 'force', 'in', 'order', 'to', 'be', 'taken', 'seriously', ',', 'and', 'that', 'you', 'have', 'to', 'spend', 'on', 'this', 'dimension', ',', "''", 'Ms.', 'Tempel', 'said', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'VBP', 'IN', "''", 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'VBN', 'RB', ',', 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-06-07_germany-pledges-to-expand-its-mi_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'It', "'s", 'not', 'just', 'Bernie', 'Sanders', 'saying', ',', '`', 'Oh', ',', 'yes', ',', 'just', 'vote', 'for', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', ',', "'", "''", 'Sanders', 'told', 'CNN', 'on', 'Sunday', '.', '``', 'It', 'is', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', 'standing', 'up', 'and', 'saying', ',', '`', 'You', 'know', 'what', '?', 'These', 'are', 'the', 'things', 'we', 'need', 'to', 'do', '.', "'", 'And', 'if', 'she', 'does', 'the', 'right', 'thing', ',', 'I', 'am', 'absolutely', 'confident', 'that', 'the', 'vast', 'majority', 'of', 'my', 'supporters', 'will', 'vote', 'for', 'her', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'RB', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBG', ',', '``', 'UH', ',', 'UH', ',', 'RB', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', "''", "''", 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBG', 'RB', 'CC', 'VBG', ',', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'WP', '.', 'DT', 'VBP', 'DT', 'NNS', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', '.', "''", 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'MD', 'VB', 'IN', 'PRP', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-27_the-revolutionary-s-next-tactic-_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'I', 'was', 'not', 'willing', 'to', 'support', 'a', 'federal', 'education', 'law', 'that', 'did', "n't", 'continue', 'to', 'monitor', 'and', 'oversee', 'the', 'progress', 'that', 'minority', 'kids', 'and', 'disabled', 'kids', 'and', 'poor', 'kids', 'are', 'making', ',', "''", 'he', 'said', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VB', 'TO', 'VB', 'CC', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'WDT', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBG', ',', "''", 'PRP', 'VBD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2015-11-30_congress-set-to-dump-no-child-le_d473'}
{'tokens': ['8:06', 'p.m.', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', 'is', 'widening', 'her', 'overall', 'delegate', 'lead', 'with', 'an', 'early', 'win', 'in', 'Florida', '.'], 'pos': ['CD', 'RB', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['TIME', 'TIME', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2016-03-15_the-latest-kasich-scores-all-del_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'The', 'Guantnamo', 'military', 'commissions', 'are', 'an', 'abject', 'failure', ',', "''", 'said', 'ACLU', 'executive', 'Director', 'Anthony', 'Romero', 'in', 'a', 'statement', '.', '``', 'They', 'have', 'never', 'worked', ',', 'are', 'not', 'working', ',', 'and', 'will', 'never', 'work', ',', 'even', 'with', 'President', 'Obama', "'s", 'well-intentioned', 'reforms', '.', 'Additionally', ',', 'the', 'president', "'s", 'continuing', 'embrace', 'of', 'indefinite', 'detention', 'without', 'charge', 'or', 'trial', 'will', 'tarnish', 'his', 'legacy', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['``', 'DT', 'NNP', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBN', ',', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBG', ',', 'CC', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', ',', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'RB', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'VBG', 'VB', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', 'MD', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-cue', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'politico_2016-02-23_obama-s-gitmo-plan-leaves-everyo_d473'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'leading', 'Republican', 'candidates', 'for', 'president', 'Thursday', 'lashed', 'out', 'at', 'President', 'Obama', 'and', 'his', 'would-be', 'Democratic', 'successor', ',', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', ',', 'in', 'a', 'debate', 'that', 'threatened', 'to', 'make', 'or', 'break', 'some', 'of', 'their', 'campaigns', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'RP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBD', 'TO', 'VB', 'CC', 'VB', 'DT', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-01-15_republicans-pile-on-obama-clinto_d473'}
{'tokens': ['Ms.', 'Gil', 'took', 'particular', 'joy', 'in', 'skating', 'outside', 'the', 'park', ',', 'popping', 'nollie', 'flips', ',', 'shove-its', 'and', 'other', 'tricks', 'in', 'front', 'of', 'the', 'nearby', 'condominium', 'complexes', ',', 'which', 'have', 'risen', 'as', 'part', 'of', 'a', 'continuing', 'wave', 'of', 'development', 'in', 'the', 'area', '.', 'To', 'Ms.', 'Gil', ',', 'skateboarding', 'represents', 'a', 'cry', 'of', 'dissent', 'against', 'the', 'city', "'s", 'gentrification', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'VBG', 'NN', 'VBZ', ',', 'NNS', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', ',', 'WDT', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'VBG', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-content'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-07-31_sisterhood-of-the-skateboard_d473'}
{'tokens': ['After', 'losing', 'big', 'on', 'gun', 'control', ',', 'yet', 'again', ',', 'this', 'week', ',', 'Democrats', 'are', 'shifting', 'full-on', 'to', 'election', 'mode', '.', 'Their', 'argument', ':', 'Only', 'a', 'Democratic', 'Senate', 'can', 'make', 'any', 'headway', 'on', 'the', 'issue', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'RB', 'RB', ',', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'NNPS', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'TO', 'NN', 'NN', '.', 'PRP$', 'NN', ':', 'RB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-06-22_what-will-it-take-for-the-senate_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['During', 'the', 'Cold', 'War', ',', 'many', 'followed', 'President', 'Reagan', "'s", 'dictum', 'that', 'the', 'Soviet', 'Union', 'was', 'an', '``', 'evil', 'empire', "''", 'bent', 'on', 'world', 'domination', '.', 'NATO', 'was', 'formed', 'to', 'contain', 'its', 'expansionist', 'ambitions', '.', 'Nuclear', 'arsenals', 'were', 'erected', 'against', 'it', '.', 'American', 'arms', 'flooded', 'into', 'anti-Soviet', 'client', 'states', '.', 'Proxy', 'battles', 'and', 'covert', 'coups', 'were', 'run', 'from', 'the', 'White', 'House', ',', 'the', 'Department', 'of', 'Defense', ',', 'the', 'CIA', 'and', 'the', 'National', 'Security', 'Agency', 'in', 'order', 'to', 'thwart', 'the', 'designs', 'of', 'fledgling', 'revolutions', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'JJ', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', '``', 'JJ', 'NN', "''", 'JJ', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', '.', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP', '.', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', '.', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'CC', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-05-11_millennials-don-t-get-socialism-_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['Like', 'the', 'page', ':', 'Republican', 'candidate', 'Lindsey', 'Graham', 'said', 'that', 'Carson', 'is', 'a', '``', 'good', ',', 'decent', 'man', ',', "''", 'and', 'said', 'that', 'Trump', '``', 'melted', 'down', 'last', 'night', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'NN', ':', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'DT', '``', 'JJ', ',', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'CC', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', '``', 'VBN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'west-journal_2015-11-13_ben-carson-just-dropped-a-powerf_d473'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'I', 'filed', 'my', 'PFD', '(', 'Personal', 'Financial', 'Disclosure', ')', ',', 'which', 'I', 'am', 'proud', 'to', 'say', 'is', 'the', 'largest', 'in', 'the', 'history', 'of', 'the', 'FEC', ',', "''", 'Trump', 'said', 'in', 'a', 'press', 'release', '.', 'The', 'candidate', 'claims', 'his', 'net', 'worth', 'is', 'in', 'excess', 'of', '$', '10', 'billion', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'PRP$', 'NN', '-LRB-', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', '-RRB-', ',', 'WDT', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', '.', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', '$', 'CD', 'CD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'west-journal_2016-05-17_trump-files-largest-financial-st_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['Roberta', 'A.', 'Kaplan', ',', 'a', 'New', 'York-based', 'lawyer', 'who', 'represented', 'plaintiffs', 'in', 'the', 'adoption', 'case', 'and', 'the', 'HB', '1523', 'lawsuit', ',', 'invoked', 'the', 'state', "'s", 'racially', 'segregated', 'history', 'in', 'hearings', 'in', 'June', '.', '``', 'There', 'ca', "n't", 'be', 'separate', 'but', 'equal', 'marriage', ',', "''", 'she', 'told', 'Reeves', '.', '``', 'There', 'ca', "n't", 'be', 'Jim', 'Crow', 'kind', 'of', 'gay', 'marriage', 'in', 'the', 'state', 'of', 'Mississippi', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'CD', 'NN', ',', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'RB', 'VBN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'EX', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'JJ', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'PRP', 'VBD', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'EX', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-07-02_judge-blocks-mississippi-s-relig_d473'}
{'tokens': ['But', 'underneath', 'the', 'sometimes', 'snarky', 'criticism', ',', 'Democratic', 'sources', 'said', ',', 'Axelrod', 'still', 'has', 'respect', 'for', 'the', 'former', 'secretary', 'of', 'state', '.', 'Any', 'bad', 'blood', 'from', 'the', '2008', 'campaign', 'was', 'put', 'aside', 'when', 'Clinton', 'joined', 'the', 'Obama', 'administration', '.'], 'pos': ['CC', 'IN', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', ',', 'NNP', 'RB', 'VBZ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', '.', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'CD', 'NN', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'RB', 'WRB', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-03-10_hillary-clinton-s-backseat-drive_d473'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'I', 'think', 'that', 'you', 'do', "n't", 'have', 'any', 'more', 'trouble', 'with', 'what', 'Trump', 'said', 'than', 'when', 'Sotomayor', 'said', 'that', '--', 'when', 'she', 'was', 'found', 'saying', 'in', 'speeches', 'that', ',', 'quote', ',', '`', 'A', 'wise', 'Latina', 'woman', 'with', 'the', 'richness', 'of', 'her', 'experience', 'would', 'more', 'often', 'than', 'not', 'reach', 'a', 'better', 'conclusion', 'than', 'a', 'white', 'male', ',', "'''", 'Grassley', 'said', 'in', 'a', 'conference', 'call', 'with', 'Iowa', 'reporters', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJR', 'NN', 'IN', 'WP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'WRB', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', ':', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', ',', 'NN', ',', '``', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'MD', 'RBR', 'RB', 'IN', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJR', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'CD', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'huff-post_2016-06-08_chuck-grassley-compares-trump-s-_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['Mr.', 'Ryan', 'has', 'long', 'said', 'that', 'he', 'will', 'support', 'the', 'party', "'s", 'nominee', ',', 'even', 'as', 'he', 'has', 'taken', 'frequent', 'shots', 'at', 'Mr.', 'Trump', "'s", 'comments', '.', 'But', 'many', 'Republicans', 'expect', 'that', 'if', 'Mr.', 'Trump', 'prevails', ',', 'Mr.', 'Ryan', 'will', 'avoid', 'directly', 'helping', 'him', ',', 'choosing', 'instead', 'to', 'shore', 'up', 'vulnerable', 'House', 'Republicans', ',', 'particularly', 'those', 'who', 'may', 'be', 'running', 'away', 'from', 'Mr.', 'Trump', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'RB', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNS', '.', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'IN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'MD', 'VB', 'RB', 'VBG', 'PRP', ',', 'VBG', 'RB', 'TO', 'VB', 'RP', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNPS', ',', 'RB', 'DT', 'WP', 'MD', 'VB', 'VBG', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-content'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-04-12_ryan-wages-campaign-to-counter-t_d473'}
{'tokens': ['Trump', 'got', '18', 'first-place', 'votes', 'this', 'week', ',', 'Marco', 'Rubio', 'got', 'seven', 'and', 'Ted', 'Cruz', 'got', 'three', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'VBD', 'CD', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'CD', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'CD', '.'], 'ner': ['PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2015-11-25_carson-is-cratering-while-trump-_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['More', 'than', '6', 'in', '10', 'Republicans', 'who', 'attended', 'the', 'caucuses', 'described', 'themselves', 'as', 'evangelical', 'Christians', ',', 'a', 'slightly', 'higher', 'percentage', 'than', 'four', 'years', 'ago', '.', 'About', 'four', 'in', '10', 'said', 'they', 'were', '``', 'angry', "''", 'with', 'the', 'way', 'the', 'federal', 'government', 'is', 'operating', '.', 'Almost', 'half', 'said', 'they', 'wanted', 'a', 'nominee', 'from', 'outside', 'the', 'political', 'establishment', ',', 'compared', 'with', 'four', 'in', '10', 'who', 'said', 'they', 'preferred', 'someone', 'with', 'political', 'experience', '.'], 'pos': ['JJR', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBN', 'PRP', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJR', 'NN', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'RB', '.', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'CD', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'VBD', '``', 'JJ', "''", 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBG', '.', 'RB', 'NN', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'VBN', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'CD', 'WP', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-02-02_no-clear-favorites-going-into-ne_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'Chinese', 'finance', 'minister', 'jabbed', 'back', 'on', 'Monday', 'at', 'complaints', 'from', 'his', 'American', 'counterpart', 'that', 'China', "'s", 'glut', 'of', 'factories', 'making', 'unwanted', 'mountains', 'of', 'steel', ',', 'aluminum', 'and', 'other', 'products', 'were', 'overwhelming', 'foreign', 'markets', 'and', 'makers', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBD', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'NN', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-06-07_china-rebuts-american-criticism-_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['Contributing', ':', 'Todd', 'Spangler', '.'], 'pos': ['VBG', ':', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-07-22_drama-doesn-t-slow-partying_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['For', 'Mr.', 'Biden', ',', 'after', 'nearly', 'eight', 'years', 'in', 'the', 'nation', "'s", 'chief', 'supporting', 'role', ',', 'the', 'appearance', 'hinted', 'at', 'the', 'niche', 'he', 'sees', 'for', 'himself', 'as', 'Election', 'Day', 'nears', ':', 'a', 'figure', 'who', 'can', 'argue', ',', 'plainly', 'and', 'personally', ',', 'that', 'Mr.', 'Trump', 'has', 'already', 'imperiled', 'the', 'nation', 'he', 'aspires', 'to', 'lead', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'IN', 'RB', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', 'VBG', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'PRP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', ':', 'DT', 'NN', 'WP', 'MD', 'VB', ',', 'RB', 'CC', 'RB', ',', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-08-17_biden-calls-trump-risk-to-u-s-sa_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'last', 'question', 'at', 'the', 'event', 'was', 'from', 'a', 'young', 'child', ',', 'who', 'said', 'he', 'and', 'his', 'father', 'drove', 'to', 'the', 'event', 'from', 'Omaha', ',', 'Nebraska', '--', 'about', 'six', 'hours', 'away', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'WP', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'VBD', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', ':', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'RB', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'politico_2016-08-11_pence-blames-media-for-trump-s-o_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['If', 'the', 'negligence', 'law', 'has', 'never', 'had', 'its', 'day', 'in', 'court', ',', 'Giuliani', 'said', ',', 'there', "'s", 'a', 'simple', 'explanation', ':', '``', 'There', "'s", 'never', 'been', 'a', 'secretary', 'of', 'State', 'who', 'has', 'been', 'as', 'reckless', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBD', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'VBD', ',', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ':', '``', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'IN', 'JJ', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'politico_2016-07-05_criminal-charges-against-clinton_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['He', 'has', 'coined', 'a', 'new', 'phrase', ',', '``', 'undocumented', 'Democrats', ',', "''", 'to', 'describe', 'those', 'in', 'the', 'country', 'illegally', ',', 'and', 'beefed', 'up', 'sections', 'of', 'his', 'stump', 'speech', 'focused', 'on', 'immigration', '.', 'He', 'expressed', 'amusement', 'that', 'Mr.', 'Rubio', 'had', 'at', 'last', 'described', 'his', 'views', 'on', 'immigration', '``', 'not', 'only', 'on', 'Spanish-language', 'television', 'but', 'on', 'English-language', 'television', ',', "''", 'echoing', 'some', 'far-right', 'commentators', 'who', 'have', 'suggested', 'that', 'Mr.', 'Rubio', 'is', 'more', 'willing', 'to', 'present', 'himself', 'as', 'a', 'pragmatist', 'on', 'the', 'issue', 'when', 'speaking', 'Spanish', '.'], 'pos': ['PRP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', '``', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', "''", 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'RB', ',', 'CC', 'VBD', 'RP', 'NNS', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NN', '.', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'JJ', 'VBD', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', '``', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', "''", 'VBG', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'WP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RBR', 'JJ', 'TO', 'JJ', 'PRP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'WRB', 'VBG', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'breitbart_2015-12-21_nytimes-casually-conflates-ted-c_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'Daily', 'Beast', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'NNP', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'huff-post_2016-05-11_sanders-told-a-female-reporter-n_d473'}
{'tokens': ['For', 'example', ',', 'Trump', "'s", 'recent', 'evidence-free', 'assertion', 'that', '``', 'thousands', "''", 'of', 'Muslim', 'Americans', 'in', 'New', 'Jersey', 'celebrated', 'the', 'fall', 'of', 'the', 'World', 'Trade', 'Center', 'towers', 'on', '9/11', 'parallels', 'stories', 'that', 'have', 'appeared', 'in', 'various', 'forms', 'in', 'chain', 'emails', 'and', 'elsewhere', 'on', 'the', 'Web', 'for', 'years', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'POS', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', '``', 'NNS', "''", 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNPS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'NNS', 'WDT', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'DURATION', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2015-12-13_misinformation-enters-mainstream_4e07'}
{'tokens': ['The', 'two', 'voters', 'acknowledged', 'that', 'both', 'Trump', 'and', 'Sanders', 'are', 'tapping', 'into', 'the', 'same', 'anti-establishment', 'anger', 'and', 'seem', 'to', 'be', 'attracting', 'the', 'most', 'passionate', 'and', 'enthusiastic', 'supporters', 'on', 'the', 'campaign', 'trail', 'this', 'cycle', '.', 'The', 'friends', 'admitted', 'the', 'dynamic', 'between', 'the', 'two', 'of', 'them', 'most', 'likely', 'does', 'not', 'reflect', 'most', 'Trump', 'and', 'Sanders', 'supporters', '.'], 'pos': ['DT', 'CD', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'VBG', 'DT', 'RBS', 'JJ', 'CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'DT', 'NN', '.', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'CD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'RBS', 'RB', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VB', 'RBS', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'huff-post_2016-02-12_the-unlikely-friendship-of-a-tru_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['In', '2011', ',', 'Weiner', 'resigned', 'from', 'Congress', '--', 'and', 'became', 'the', 'fodder', 'of', 'late-night', 'comedians', '--', 'after', 'he', 'accidentally', 'posted', 'a', 'sexually', 'explicit', 'image', 'of', 'himself', 'on', 'Twitter', '.', 'Although', 'Weiner', 'attempted', 'to', 'revive', 'his', 'political', 'career', 'in', '2013', 'by', 'running', 'for', 'New', 'York', 'City', 'mayor', ',', 'he', 'lost', 'the', 'election', 'amid', 'a', 'second', 'sexting', 'scandal', '(', 'the', 'one', 'where', 'he', 'used', 'the', 'alias', 'Carlos', 'Danger', ')', '.', 'Afterward', ',', 'Weiner', 'mostly', 'dropped', 'out', 'of', 'the', 'public', 'eye', ',', 'giving', 'only', 'occasional', 'interviews', 'with', 'the', 'media', '.', 'He', 'announced', 'that', 'he', 'was', 'undergoing', 'therapy', 'and', 'vowed', 'to', 'focus', 'on', 'being', 'a', 'better', 'father', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'CD', ',', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', ':', 'CC', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', ':', 'IN', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', ',', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', '-LRB-', 'DT', 'CD', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNS', 'NNP', 'NNP', '-RRB-', '.', 'RB', ',', 'NNP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'IN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'VBG', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', '.', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'VBG', 'NN', 'CC', 'VBD', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'JJR', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'DATE', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'huff-post_2016-08-29_anthony-weiner-reportedly-caught_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'I', "'ve", 'ruined', 'your', 'good', 'reputation', ',', 'huh', '?', "''", 'he', 'responded', '.'], 'pos': ['``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'RB', '.', "''", 'PRP', 'VBD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2016-07-25_sanders-endorsement-for-some_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['I', 'recently', 'received', 'this', '28-page', 'tsunami', 'of', 'questions', 'about', 'everything', 'from', 'my', 'plumbing', 'to', 'my', 'profession', 'to', 'my', 'ethnicity', 'and', 'income', '.', 'But', 'as', 'a', 'former', 'Census-taker', 'who', 'has', 'written', 'about', 'Census', 'controversies', 'for', 'more', 'than', '25', 'years', ',', 'Trump', "'s", 'words', 'today', 'and', 'the', 'bureau', "'s", 'actions', 'in', 'the', 'past', 'make', 'me', 'wary', 'of', 'this', 'blunderbuss', '.'], 'pos': ['PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'TO', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'TO', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', '.', 'CC', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'IN', 'JJR', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', ',', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNS', 'NN', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'VB', 'PRP', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'O'], 'id': 'usa-today_2015-11-24_trump-card-for-census-roundup-bu_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['BEFORE', 'YOU', 'GO', '.'], 'pos': ['IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'huff-post_2016-01-12_tuesday-s-morning-email-presiden_6b86'}
{'tokens': ['But', 'two', 'out', 'of', 'three', 'Americans', 'still', 'feel', 'the', 'country', 'is', 'on', 'the', 'wrong', 'path', ',', 'in', 'part', 'because', 'the', 'gains', 'of', 'the', 'last', 'few', 'years', 'have', 'not', 'been', 'distributed', 'evenly', '.', 'Income', 'disparities', 'have', 'grown', 'worse', '.', 'The', 'poverty', 'rate', 'is', '14.8', 'percent', ',', 'higher', 'than', 'when', 'Mr.', 'Obama', 'took', 'office', '.', 'The', 'economy', 'is', 'growing', 'again', ',', 'but', 'not', 'as', 'fast', 'as', 'under', 'Ronald', 'Reagan', 'or', 'Bill', 'Clinton', '.', 'And', 'although', 'the', 'deficit', 'has', 'been', 'slashed', 'from', 'its', 'recession', 'spike', ',', 'the', 'overall', 'national', 'debt', 'has', 'ballooned', 'to', '$', '18', 'trillion', 'from', '$', '11', 'trillion', '.'], 'pos': ['CC', 'CD', 'IN', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'RB', 'VBP', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBN', 'VBN', 'RB', '.', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'JJR', '.', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'CD', 'NN', ',', 'JJR', 'IN', 'WRB', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NN', '.', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'RB', ',', 'CC', 'RB', 'RB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.', 'CC', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'TO', '$', 'CD', 'CD', 'IN', '$', 'CD', 'CD', '.'], 'ner': ['O', 'NUMBER', 'O', 'O', 'NUMBER', 'MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'DURATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERCENT', 'PERCENT', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'B-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'I-source', 'B-cue', 'I-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'nyt_2016-01-14_america-the-shiny-or-gloomy-obam_5fec'}
{'tokens': ['Warren', 'may', 'play', 'role', 'in', 'push', 'to', 'broker', 'peace', 'between', 'Clinton', ',', 'Sanders', '.'], 'pos': ['NNP', 'MD', 'VB', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', '.'], 'ner': ['MISC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O'], 'labels': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-09_party-aims-to-heal-primary-wound_ef2d'}
{'tokens': ['``', 'Just', 'because', 'people', 'assume', 'Hillary', 'is', 'part', 'of', 'the', 'system', 'does', "n't", 'mean', 'she', 'wo', "n't", 'make', 'changes', ',', "''", 'Nguyen', 'said', '.', '``', 'I', 'am', 'frustrated', '.', 'The', 'middle', 'class', 'is', 'shrinking', ',', 'and', 'I', 'am', 'the', 'middle', 'class', '.', 'But', 'it', 'would', 'be', 'chaos', 'to', 'overthrow', 'the', 'system', '.', "''"], 'pos': ['``', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VB', 'PRP', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'NNS', ',', "''", 'NNP', 'VBD', '.', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'JJ', '.', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBG', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', 'CC', 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'B-source', 'B-cue', 'O', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'wash-post_2016-06-01_voters-skeptical-as-clinton-vows_4b22'}
{'tokens': ['CNN', 'President', 'On', 'Trump', ':', '`', 'We', 'Do', 'Not', 'Pay', 'Candidates', 'To', 'Appear', 'At', 'Debates', '.', "'"], 'pos': ['NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', ':', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNS', '.', "''"], 'ner': ['ORGANIZATION', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O'], 'labels': ['B-source', 'I-source', 'O', 'O', 'B-cue', 'B-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content', 'I-content'], 'id': 'huff-post_2015-12-03_cnn-president-on-trump-we-do-not_4e07'}
